♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Trick or treat?!
Chris, what in God's name
are you doing?
Y-You can't go out
dressed like that.
Why not? I'm Bill Cosby.
Okay, but, I mean,
y-you can't go out like that.
Well, come on, Mom,
don't I look like him?
(imitating Bill Cosby
with slurred mumbling)
Well, yes, but, Chris, you can't
just walk around in blackface.
It's racist.
Now, go upstairs and put on
that Indian chief costume
I bought you.
Aw, I don't want to!
(slurred muttering)
Peter, what's with
all the eggs?
Oh, well, every Halloween,
me, Joe and Quagmire
do this thing where
one of us is it,
and then the
other two of us
nail the crap out of him
with awesome pranks.
Well, who's it this year?
Damn it.
(gasps)
(screaming)
Guys, guys, be careful!
This isn't my box!
Oh, yeah, sure.
Then whose is it?
MAN:
It's mine.
I'm Dick Pump,
and I'd appreciate it
if you hooligans didn't get
your eggs all over my parcel.
Sorry. I keep getting
your mail, Dick.
Hey, what's in there, anyway?
Embarrassing stuff.
Wow, that was
terrific, Jessica.
It was good for me, too.
(screams)
(laughing)
Got-got you again, Quagmire.
You said you were that
waitress from Friendly's!
I lied.
You jerk!
I didn't feel anything.
But you did!
Happy Halloween,
(bleep).
Hey, hey, get away!
Just get away
from me, Peter!
Hey, take it easy, Quagmire.
Nobody wants to hurt you.
Right, Joe?
Gotcha!
Ha! Hepatitis-C!
Joke's on you;
I already got it.
Meningitis!
I'm a carrier.
Gonorrhea!
Patient Zero.
You're gonna have to do
better than that.
I don't know, Joe.
That's it.
We're out of known diseases.
Unless...
All right, what this is has
no name, so you can't have it.
(mosquito buzzing)
(chuckles)
We got him.
Halloween is fun.
What was that?
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
I knew this day would come.
Rupert, we're under attack
by monsters!
Dear God!
Oh, but wait, there's Superman.
He'll save us.
Superman! Superman!
Wait, wait.
Where are you going?!
Ah, to hell with him.
We'll have to deal with
these marauders ourselves.
Rupert, man your station.
All right, you undead bastards,
time to send you back to hell!
(Stewie yelling, kids screaming)
Hey, Stewie, you all set
to go trick-or-treating?
Whoa, what the hell
are you doing?!
We're under attack, Brian!
By zombies and vampires
and a Mexican princess!
Stewie, those aren't monsters,
they're kids.
They're trick-or-treaters.
Trick-or-treaters?
Yeah. It's what kids do
on Halloween.
They-they dress up
in costumes,
and they go around
asking for candy.
How do you not know
about trick-or-treating?
Well, how do you not know
that your reflection
in the patio door
isn't another dog?
Hey! That guy is a dick.
Hey, get out of here!
This is my house!
Oh, my God, Brian.
What happened?
Who did this to you?
Did you do this?!
You son of a bitch!
Okay, see you
later, Mom.
Oh, where are you
off to, sweetie?
You gonna go see
three movies in a row
so it seems like
you're out doing something?
No, Mom. I'm going to my first
big high school Halloween party.
Oh, that's nice.
What are you dressed as?
I'm a slutty cat.
I'll be back late.
Don't wait up.
Quack, quack.
Oh! My little ducky.
You look so adorable.
Oh, no, no.
You see these holes?
I got bit by a vampire.
I'm a vampire duck.
But I'm a modern vampire duck
who hangs around
with Anna Paquin and drives
around in a black Mercedes.
What is that?
It's True Blood.
Yeah, no one knows
what that is.
Rich, gay people do.
Brian, are you sure
none of these are real monsters?
Stewie, it's
gonna be fine.
Look, here's
our first house.
There you go.
A Cornish game hen for you,
a Cornish game hen for you.
Everybody gets a hen.
Would you like
some gravy?
Sure you'd like
some gravy.
Oh, my God, Brian,
you were right.
Halloween is
the best.
Look how much candy I have.
Oh, w-where should we go next?
Ooh, look, there's Mort's house.
Oh, but I hope he doesn't have
some gross Jewish candy,
like-like Rugelach
or-or Hamentashen
or-or Hachahachahacha.
R-Right, Brian?
Brian?
Brian, where are you?
Hey, kid,
nice costume.
Really?
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
My mother bought it for me,
and I was worried
it might be a tad banal,
but if you big kids like it,
then it must be pretty cool.
That's a nice bag
of candy you've got.
Oh, thank you.
You know, it's actually
a pillowcase.
Th-They're sort of thrifty
around my house, you know.
Well, now it's ours.
Uh, well, no.
But how about this?
You can have the apple
and the raisins
and the cheese and crackers
with the little red stick.
I don't, I don't know
how that's candy, but...
Thanks, duck boy.
(laughter)
Hey, get back here!
Hey, that's my candy!
Damn you, that's my candy!
Oh, how could this day
get any worse?
(mosquito buzzing)
(screams)
Brian! Brian, help me! Brian!
Hey, there you are.
Brian, where were you?
Well, that jerk dog
from our patio door
somehow got inside a hubcap.
I just wanted to alert
the owner of the car.
I left a note
on his windshield.
Wh-What is wrong with you?
You abandoned me!
And some larger
children took my candy.
Al-All right, look,
just calm down.
It's still early.
We'll get you more candy.
Brian, this
isn't working.
What do you want me
to do, Stewie? It's late.
Everybody's stopped
giving out candy.
Well, then let's get
my candy back, Brian.
Let's track down the punks who
stole it and make them pay.
Look, Stewie,
I don't think that...
Brian, please.
This is my first Halloween,
and-and it's ruined.
(sighs)
All right, all right, fine.
We'll look for them.
Good, because so far,
Halloween's a bigger letdown
than being a Mets fan.
ANNOUNCER:
Opening day, and here's
the first pitch.
(bat cracks)
And the season's over.
Ah, you were a good sport
this year, Quagmire.
Ah, well, you know, Peter,
it's all in good fun, right?
You know, my grandfather
used to have a saying...
(speaking Japanese)
Holy crap, you speak Ebonics?
No, no, Peter,
it's Japanese.
Wait, are they,
are they the angry eye ones
or the tired eye ones?
Uh, I-I'm not
sure I underst--
Uh, the first
one, I guess.
I-I don't know.
M-My grandfather on my
mom's side was Japanese.
Wait a minute,
you're-you're part Japanese?
Sure am.
My grandfather
was a pilot
for the Imperial Air Force
during World War Two.
Flew a kamikaze mission
in the Battle of Midway.
He's part of the reason
I became a pilot.
Wow. How come
I never met him?
He was a
kamikaze pilot.
Yeah, no, I heard you,
he was a Karma Chameleon,
but how-how come
I never met him?
Because he
died, Peter.
Oh, my God, when?
And how?
Hey, Joe,
what are you doing?
I thought we were gonna go
to The Clam and get wasted.
Ugh, I can't.
I'm on duty tonight.
And Halloween's got to be
the worst night of the year
to be a cop.
All you do is drive around,
confiscate beer from teenagers
and occasionally handcuff
a drunk woman in a sexy costume.
Aw, cool!
Hey, I got a great idea.
How about
we ride around with you
and steal beer from teenagers?
I don't know, you guys.
This is my job, and I can't
have you fooling around,
getting into trouble.
Hey, when the hell
do I get into trouble?
Well, didn't you get lost
in the grocery store last week?
(wailing)
Are you okay?
No!
I came in with my wife
and now I can't find her!
Oh, I'm sure
she's here somewhere.
Come on,
I'll help you find her.
Okay.
(over P.A.):
Will Lois Griffin please
come to the courtesy booth.
We have a little
gift for you.
(giggles)
I'm Lois-- Oh, for
God's sakes, Peter.
Yay, Lois!
This is so cool.
Our first high school
Halloween party.
Do you think
we'll get to make out?
These things always end up
in make out sessions.
Hey, you know what,
you guys?
My cousin went to
a Halloween party
and made out with a guy,
and she's hideous.
I mean, really hideous.
How'd your cousin
do it?
She wore a mask.
Don't you get it?
If we wear our masks
and we don't take them off
for the whole party, the
boys won't know who we are,
and we'll have a better
chance of hooking up.
Good idea!
We are so
gonna hook up!
I think we look hot.
Totally hot.
Ugly bitches!
Moo!
JOE:
So what's the story, Quagmire?
Do you observe any particular
Japanese customs?
QUAGMIRE:
Oh, yeah, I'm very in
touch with my Asian roots.
You notice I take my shoes off
whenever I enter my house.
PETER:
Oh, yeah.
I do five hours of math
homework every night
even though I'm
no longer in school.
Ah.
Sometimes I drink
out of a wooden box.
Ooh.
Ah, very Asian.
I was a very cute baby and
now I'm a joyless adult.
Ah.
They are unhappy.
DISPATCHER:
All units, we've got a domestic
disturbance at Fifth and Maple.
This is Officer Swanson
responding, I'm on my way.
All right you guys, these
domestic dispute situations
can get pretty dicey, so I need
you to stay in the car, okay?
No joking around.
All right, sir, sir, ma'am.
I just need you to tell me
clearly and calmly,
what happened.
One at a time, please.
This whore gets her stubby little
fingers into my wallet! That's larceny!
He puts one of those cigars in his mouth
and he turns into a different person!
PETER:
No freakin' way.
Guys, I told you
to wait in the car.
Domestic abuse is a
very delicate matter.
Joe, this isn't domestic
abuse, this is hilarious.
And another thing--
I'm tired of massaging
your foot knuckles!
You call that a massage,
with your baby carrot fingers?!
Go to hell!
Come here!
Get over here!
Stay away from me!
You keep him away from me!
You little...!
(both yelling)
Get over here!
I'm gonna jump over you
and I'm gonna... !
Come back here!
All right, that's
enough, you two.
This is serious. Stop it.
(all yelling)
Oh, quick, Quagmire,
give me your iPod.
(comedic, carnival-like music
playing; yelling continues)
WOMAN:
I swear to God!
You keep him away from me!
JOE:
Got 'em.
Aw, they got tuckered out.
Of course they did, they ran
like two miles for them.
Okay, there they are, Brian.
And they've still got my candy.
You distract them, and I'll run
up from behind and grab it.
Stewie, don't be ridiculous.
They're kids,
and I'm an adult.
I'll just go over there and calmly
ask them to give back the candy.
Hi, fellas.
Hey, look,
it's Snoopy.
Hey, Snoopy,
where's Woodstock?
Ah, that-- that's a good one.
Uh, listen, my friend,
Stewie, he's just a baby,
and you guys took
his candy earlier.
What do you say
you just give it back,
and we all forget
this ever happened?
Sure, why not?
Your friend's candy is
right around the corner.
All right. Terrific.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Stop it!
(spray can hissing)
Hey, let me go! No! No!
(Brian screaming)
Oh my God, you
look so cute.
What is that, spray paint?
Yeah. Those little
punks want a war.
And now they've got one.
Hey, here's someone who
might understand how you feel.
Hey, how you doing.
First day being pink?
Yeah.
Welcome to hell.
(dramatic musical sting)
All right, Brian,
we're getting my candy back,
and here's how
it's gonna go down:
First, we track down those teenage
hoodlums and kill them all.
Yeah, okay, fine,
let's kill 'em.
Wha-- really? No way.
No, I was only half serious.
We can't do that.
Oh, my God-- Pink Brian
is crazy Brian.
Oh, man.
I know, I know we can't.
I just feel bad they
stole your candy.
Well, now I know how Peter feels
when Mort steals his paper.
Come on, that's right,
you bastard.
Stop right there!
Give me the paper!
No! No! Don't hurt me,
you bastard.
Mort, give me the paper.
No, I'm reading it in here.
You can have the
real estate section.
It's for schmucks, anyway.
Okay, your turn
to spin the bottle,
guy dressed like Bill Clinton.
(chuckles)
Yeah, dressed like.
All right, let's go make
some Whitewater.
Okay, Slutty Cat,
you're up next.
Oh my God, this is
totally working.
Nobody knows who we are.
All right. Slutty Cat
and Optimus Prime.
Into the closet.
(giggling)
Oh, my God, you're
gonna hook up.
With a boy.
I know. I can't believe it.
Oh, I feel as pretty
as Scarlett Johansson.
PHOTOGRAPHERS:
Scarlett!
Scarlett Johansson!
Scarlett Johansson! Scarlett!
Scarlett!
Laura Linney.
Whoops.
(kissing sounds)
Come on, you guys.
It's been well
over seven minutes.
(passionate moaning)
Let's go.
Other people want
to use the closet.
You guys...
(gasps)
Oh.... my... God.
Chris?
Meg?
(screaming)
Oh, my God, what are
you doing here?!
Trying to grab some boob!
From your sister?!
I didn't know it was you!
Well, who did you think it was?!
Some bitch! Who cares?!
(retching)
Oh, my God!
Oh. We did so much!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
We're disgusting!
We're a disgrace
to our family!
Oh, maybe I can
get in on this.
Oh, it's good to finally
be off duty.
Wow, I never knew about
this place, Quagmire.
Yeah, this is
the Air Force graveyard,
where old military planes
come to die.
That one over there
is my favorite.
It's an old Japanese Zero.
Wow, no calories and all
that Japanese taste?
That's the kind of plane
my grandfather used to
fly in the war. Cool.
Man, this thing looks like it
still might be in working order.
You guys want to go for a ride?
Ah, sure.
Hell, yeah.
Wow, I always thought the
Japanese flew flying saucers.
All right, there they are.
All right, boys,
it's candy time.
Let's dig in.
Okay, Brian, let's do this.
Give me a boost.
Hello.
Hey, it's that stupid kid.
Yes, it's that stupid kid.
Now, listen very closely, 'cause
here's how it's gonna go down.
(roaring)
(cheering)
Guys, guys, guys,
I don't want to toot my own horn
here, but I think that was me.
(yells)
Well, there's only one thing
to do now: go to plan B.
Mom!
I am so sorry, Mrs. Griffin.
I have no idea what
got into my son.
Well, just have him return
the candy and everything's fine.
Justin, you give this young man
his candy back, right now.
All right, here.
Thanks.
Now, we want Justin's candy.
What?
You heard me.
Take Justin's bag of candy
and pour it into Stewie's.
All of it.
And if I think you're
holding back on me,
we're gonna have
a serious problem.
Well, all right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, serious problem.
Good. Now, go in your purse,
take out $40
and put it in the bag.
All right, Lois, you're
kind of scaring me now.
I-I-I don't have $40.
All right, I understand.
I'll be back tomorrow
for the $80.
And I'm taking
your welcome mat.
Whoa, Quahog looks
beautiful from up here.
Yeah, this thing handles
pretty smooth, doesn't it?
Feels right.
Feels kind of like something
I was meant to fly, you know.
Hey, there's Quahog Harbor.
Look at all those
old naval vessels.
Yeah, look at 'em all.
Whoa, whoa, easy, Quagmire.
What are you doing?
I don't know, Peter.
It's like something just
awakened inside me.
I can feel my grandfather's
Japanese blood
coursing through my veins.
Quagmire, what the hell's
the matter with you?
What are you nuts?
Shut up, roundeye!
Oh, my God! Stop, Quagmire!
I don't want to die.
Please don't kill us!
(shouting in Japanese)
Banzai!
Oh, God!
No!
(screaming)
You know what they call this
in my country?
What?! What?!
Payback.
(panting):
What the hell was that?
Prank's on
you, (bleep).
I'm not Japanese.
You're not?
No.
That was for making me have sex
with Joe, you sons of bitches.
You guys actually had sex?
Yeah, I kind of went
rogue with that one.
Brian, you took me out on my
first Halloween tonight,
and you showed me
an exciting time.
And for that,
I'm going to let you
pick out some candy from my bag.
Oh, thanks.
And keep in mind, we can't use
any actual brand names
due to advertising concerns.
Right, okay, I'll have
a Mr. Whip-o Bar,
a Kooky Nut Pop,
some Jim 'n M's,
uh, a Zip Zap,
a Choco Buddy,
uh, a Sixty-Four-
Thousand-Dollar Bar,
a Notafinger
and a Dawkin's
Peanut Butter Disc.
God, I hate television.
Brian, why are you pink?
(sniffs)
Why do you and Meg smell
like sweat and shame?
Uh, well... you see,
um... we, uh...
You know what?
I don't care.
I hooked up with
a chick tonight,
and I am pretty darn
proud of myself.
You're right, Chris.
I hooked up
with a guy tonight--
a high school guy--
and I think maybe
he'll call tomorrow.
You may be disappointed.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru